

CONTACT

Address: Bilker Allee 140,

40217 Düsseldorf
Phone :+49 1729471513
E-Mail : mano.hicet@gmail.com

GitHub & LinkedIn

- GitHub URL
- LinkedIn URL

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Technologies

- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS3

Javascript Frameworks

- React
- jQuery
- Express JS
- Node JSWeb Layout

Databases

- MongoDB
- MYSOL
- Oracle
- SQL Server

Version Control

• Git

Material UI

Programming

Bootstrap

- (
- C++
- Visual Basic
- Power Builder

LANGUAGES

- Tamil (Mother Tongue)
- English : Fluent (C1)
- Deutsch : Intermediate

PASSIONS

- Yoga & Meditation
- Mandala Drawing
- Cooking

MANONMANI SELVAKUMAR

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Full Stack Web Development with hands-on Experience in Teaching Computer Science Technologies who is about to graduate a 1-year Intensive Training in Full stack Web Development (MERN Stack).

Seeking an Internship Position to apply the collected earlier experience and Web Technologies to challenge myself and deliver solution-oriented approaches.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Course| Digital Career Institute | Since Jul 2020 | Düsseldorf During the Course of study, deeply exploring technologies of MERN stack by learning and applying them to various practical projects.

Designing the Front End for the final project using Material UI and JavaScript frameworks.

Deutsch C1 Language Course | IIK, Düsseldorf | Oct 2019-Feb 2020
Deutsch B2 Language Course | BBQ, Düsseldorf | Sep 2018-Mar 2019
Deutsch B1 Language Course | Benedict, Düsseldorf | May 2018-Jul 2018
Master of Philosophy(Computer Science)| Bharathiar University, India | 2005-2006
Master of Computer Applications | Bharathiar University, India | 1999-2002
Bachelors in Computer Science | Bharathiar University, India | 1996-1999

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT PROFESSOR

Swami Vivekananda PG College | Jun 2009 - May 2010 | India Conducted Postgraduate Lectures on Various areas of Computer Science and did Researching on New Subject topic areas to teach.

• PROFESSOR

Hindusthan College of Engineering & Technology| Jun 2008 - May 2009 | India Challenged and Motivated Students through in-depth lectures and discussions on WebTecnology, Computer Networks and Database Concepts.

• PROFESSOR

PSG College of Arts & Science | Jan 2003 - Nov 2006 | India

Taught Introductory and Upper Level Courses in Computer Science and Applications. Motivated and encouraged the Students to do better and achieve more by conducting Quiz and printing Monthly Magazine.

• PROGRAMMER ANALYST

Tamilnadu Infotech (P) Ltd| Jan 2003 - Nov 2006 | India

Developed a School Automation Desktop Application using PowerBuilder and SQL Server

RELEVANT PROJECTS

- Lavilla : https://manonmani-s.github.io/la_villa/
 - Using HTML and CSS designed a Responsive Web Page for Interiors and Luxury Fabrics Collections.
- Simple Bootstrap Theme :https://manonmani-s.github.io/bootstrap_exercise_kindness/#